{
    "subject": "Tuesday_Weld",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Dudley_Moore",
    "human_readable": "Tuesday Weld is married to Dudley Moore.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9884006977081299,
            "question": "Is Dudley Moore married to Tuesday Weld?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9584540128707886,
            "question": "How long have Tuesday Weld and Dudley Moore been married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9301706552505493,
            "question": "What is the relationship between Tuesday Weld and Dudley Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8995442390441895,
            "question": "Who is Tuesday Weld married to?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7957942485809326,
            "question": "Has Tuesday Weld been married before?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.748249351978302,
            "question": "Are there any famous couples in Hollywood history similar to Tuesday Weld and Dudley Moore?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7169525027275085,
            "question": "What is the name of Tuesday Weld's husband?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.43569281697273254,
            "question": "Who are some famous people that Tuesday Weld has been associated with?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.35194313526153564,
            "question": "Can you tell me more about Tuesday Weld's personal life?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.022235827520489693,
            "question": "What are some of the most well-known relationships in the entertainment industry?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Tuesday Weld is married to Dudley Moore.",
            "html": "yago_6176_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you tell me more about Tuesday Weld's personal life?",
            "html": "yago_6176_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who are some famous people that Tuesday Weld has been associated with?",
            "html": "yago_6176_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the name of Tuesday Weld's husband?",
            "html": "yago_6176_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_14.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_25.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_62.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_71.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_81.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_86.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_90.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_6176_95.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'} \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "{'output': 'yes'}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Tuesday Weld is married to Dudley Moore.\" The documents mention their marriage in multiple contexts, including details about when they got together, dated, were married, and eventually divorced."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\n      \"output\": \"yes\"\n   }"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}